Love jyushu, please check it out.
glory
This program is brought to you by six
people who are active to promote
something exciting.
Six people challenge themselves to
various things and promote exciting
dolls all over the world.
Six people challenge themselves to
various things and promote exciting
dolls all over the world.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Ready, go!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Together, Tomorrow!
The strongest love!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Together, Tomorrow!
The strongest love!
Even if it's the best day, it's the
worst day
Good job!
Tomorrow will surely be a better day
I'm sleepy
My bangs...
Ah!
I'm Hitoka!
Hello!
Today, I'm taking pictures.
Cute ribbon, right?
There's a ribbon here, too.
There's a ribbon on the waist, too.
Heart is cute, too.
Right?
Yes, yes.
I'm shooting now.
Kanamin is laughing.
I ate croissant this morning.
I made gratin last night and ate with
my family.
I made apple candy, but I failed.
I made it at first try.
I've been cooking myself recently.
I like corn soup and pumpkin soup.
I make it for my sister.
Today's lipstick is pink.
Pink.
I'm going to put on eye shadow.
It's cute.
Well, then.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
What?
I found it.
You are beautiful today, too.
You are cute, so I'm going to upload
it.
Upload.
I'm going to upload it.
Because you are cute.
Ah, so cute!
Ah!
The eyes!
Thank you so much!
Did you see that service shot?
It's wonderful!
It's a wink!
So cute!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Today, I was not live streaming, but I
was taking a picture of myself.
Why did I say live streaming?
I don't know.
It was my first live streaming since I
became a super fan.
I wore this costume and had fun with
everyone.
I think I was able to show a new side
of me this time.
Please check my live streaming after
becoming a super fan!
I think I can show you a different
feeling from usual.
And the main costume is very cute.
I'm sure I can get a live photo that I
want you to get.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you.
See you again!
I'm sure you'll be excited when the new
live photo comes out.
Please aim for the complete version and
get the live photo!
Bye bye!
The live photo shooting is over!
It was fun to be able to do it all in
one day.
It was fun.
We had an event on our own.
It was a little different from usual.
It was fun to do it all by ourselves.
It was fun.
It was a very exciting game, and we
were able to do it all by ourselves.
It was very powerful.
It was a lot of fun.
Everyone, please check it out.
Please check it out.
Thank you.
I'm so excited!
I'm number 29!
I'm number 30!
I'm number 10!
Ta-da!
I'm number 13, Kanami!
Look! I'm number 14!
I'm number 46, Ayami!
I'm number 17, Ayami!
What did you get, Pio?
What does Hiyori mean by
Number 43
Correct!
Hit it!
Hit me!
Translated by Vortex
It's so cute!
But it's not number 43.
Oh, Hiyori-chan!
Is this it?
Oh!
That's it!
It's number 43!
Hey, give me the pen!
I don't have it!
Which one will you get?
Tokimeki Live Photos!
Number 43!
Tokimeki Live Photos will have a
limited time offer of a selfie version!
I got number 26!
Oh, it was number 29.
Is this it?
Oh, that's number 43!
Hey, give me a break!
I'm in the middle of a break, but I
have a good news.
Good evening, everyone! I'm Kanamin,
a.k.a. Tsujino Kanami.
Today, I have a good news!
Yeah!
It's a couple song from Tomorrow's
Strongest Group, here!
I'd like to announce the names of the
songs!
I'm so happy to announce the names of
the songs!
I hope you can guess the names of the
songs by the title of the song!
The new single, Tomorrow Saikyousetsu,
is a very positive song.
It's a song that makes you feel
positive.
The coupling song is also the best!
I'd like to announce the names of the
songs!
First, the song that is included in the
Type A version and the Type B version
is...
Oh!
恋のジャッカル
I think this song is a little bit like,
when you hear the word, jackal, you
might think,
what? What? What?
You might think of something like that.
How is it? Is it right?
Please look forward to the song.
Next is our pick for Type C!
It's one of my favorite songs and it's
really good!
I can't wait for you to hear it!
There's one more thing I like about
this song.
I love the jacket I'm wearing in the
cover of the song.
Let's go!
Last!
Type D No.1!
The one who is included in this is...
Ta-da!
I'm the No.1 girl!
It's a really cool song.
The last chorus is really cool.
Everything is cool, but I like the last
part the most.
I think you'll be able to relate to it
if you listen to it.
The choreography is really fun to dance
to.
I think you'll enjoy it, so please look
forward to it.
I can't wait to play all the songs!
I can't wait!
Please look forward to it!
Please continue to enjoy Tokiwara!
See you!
This was Hanamin! Bye bye!
We are shooting at Toshimaen today!
We had a chance to perform at the Music
Video of FASHION HEART SHAKER and also
at the live show.
I'm so happy!
We are going to ride the merry-go-
round!
Start!
Not this one!
I'm scared!
Please subscribe to my channel!
It's spinning.
We're going to eat croquettes now.
Croquettes?
It's gross.
It's like a cookie.
It's a cookie.
Croquettes.
It's like a croquette.
We're going to eat.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
I'm so happy.
I love you.
Thank you.
Callongrass
I am the hunter of the cherry blossom
I am the real monkey
Please subscribe to my channel.
Cute.
I saw it.
Hello.
You can jump.
Great.
Bye bye.
I'm going to the beach.
It's a cover.
It's so small.
I want to go inside.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm going to try to make it white.
It's getting white.
I don't know where to look.
Wait, it's looking like Jenny.
I'm going to try to make it white.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Oh, the sound...
No!
I did it!
You got in.
Reality
I was surprised.
Thank you for your viewing.
Safely you are there.
grab the ropes from behind.
Hey.
I got you
So exciting.
Please support in the comments!
Fell in love~~~
You're sky is set!
You did it!
2001 Gensokyo
Off to a brand new start
10 investir my breath
All the shibu inu
I'll threaten to assist
With my nipping technique
The final round
Achieved
owl
Invest
Remaining
All the chizuxin